Viewers all over the world, begin to reason with yourself right now.
Reason with yourself - you will see what satan might have used.
You will see what satan is using to connect you to himself.
He wants you to be unhappy, he wants you to be sad.
He wants you to look at Jesus in a bad light.
Reason with yourself - you will see what satan is using to connect you to himself.
It can be sickness, infirmity, stagnation, nightmares, loneliness or depression.
These are the tools of satan.
Whatever satan might have been using to connect you to himself -
be broken, in the name of Jesus!
You want to be happy, but when this pain, affliction and whatever challenging situation comes,
it changes your joy.
Be broken, in the name of Jesus!
When Jesus says, "Yes", no one can say, "No".
I can hear chains falling!
Chains of setback - I can hear chains falling!
Chains of stagnation - I can hear chains falling!
Chains of failure - I can hear chains falling!
Chains!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus!
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Lizz ndungu 27/10/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 17/11/2018